[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Are shops and bakeries merchant or non-market?",
    "answers": [" It depends", " Merchants ", "Non-market"],
    "correctAnswer": "Merchants"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What does the NAF code mean?",
    "answers": [
      "Nomenclature of French activities",
      "Standard of French activities",
      "Nature of French activities"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Nomenclature of French activities"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "How many digits does the Siren number have?",
    "answers": ["8", "9", "5"],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Are hairdressers merchants or non-marketers?",
    "answers": [" Non-market", "Merchants"],
    "correctAnswer": "Merchants"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What are the primary needs?",
    "answers": [
      "Food, shelter, shelter, healing",
      "Food, entertainment, sports"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Food, shelter, shelter, healing"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "Concurrent management occurs when",
    "answers": [
      "The agreement and presence of both spouses is necessary to administer common property",
      "Only a spouse has the power to administer his or her own property",
      "Each spouse has the power to administer a common property alone"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Each spouse has the power to administer a common property alone"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "In principle, acts of disposal relating to furniture are subject to:",
    "answers": [
      " Joint management (co-management)",
      "Concurrent management",
      "Exclusive management"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Concurrent management"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "Which of these assertions, relating to the withdrawal and transfer of powers of a spouse over joint property (Article 1426 CCiv), is false?",
    "answers": [
      "The act performed by the authorized spouse is not enforceable against the spouse in possession",
      "The competent judge is the family judge",
      "The act performed by the authorized spouse binds only the latter",
      "The spouse deprived of his powers over the common property no longer commits these funds"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "The act performed by the authorized spouse is not enforceable against the spouse in possession"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "An act is said to be connective between spouses when",
    "answers": [
      "It engages the commons",
      "It creates obligations towards both spouses",
      "It was signed by both spouses"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": " It was signed by both spouses "
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Does a donation of a spouse's earnings and wages escape co-determination?",
    "answers": [
      "Yes, always",
      "Yes, but only if they are not saved",
      "No, never"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Yes, but only if they are not saved"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "In principle, can a spouse who decides to enter into an act subject to co-determination simply warn his or her spouse to make the act valid with regard to both spouses?",
    "answers": [
      "No, it requires express consent of both spouses",
      "No, it requires the express or implied consent of both spouses",
      "Yes, a simple warning is enough"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "No, you need express or implied consent from both spouses"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "Can the donation of furniture escape co-determination?",
    "answers": [
      "Yes, thanks to the presumption of movable property governed by Article 222 CCiv",
      "No, any donation of furniture or buildings is subject to co-management"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Yes, thanks to the presumption of movable property governed by Article 222 CCiv"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "What is the process of analyzing data to make informed marketing decisions called?",
    "answers": ["Marketing Analytics", "Brand Identity"],
    "correctAnswer": "Marketing Analytics"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "Question": "Paul wants to make a legacy of a common good: he promises his wife Catherine that his legacy will not exceed his share in the community. Is he within his rights?",
    "answers": [
      "Yes",
      "No, it is forbidden to bequeath a common goodNo, it is forbidden to bequeath a common good"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "Which leases are subject to co-determination?",
    "answers": [
      "Commercial leases, rural leases, and residential leases relating to family housing",
      "Rural leases and all residential leases"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Commercial leases, rural leases, and residential leases relating to family housing"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "In the context of an express mandate between spouses, must the mandatary spouse account for the fruits he has received from the other person's own property?",
    "answers": [
      "No, unless the mandate expressly requires it to do so",
      "No, never,",
      "Yes, always"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "No, unless the mandate expressly requires it to do so"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "An act of disposition made by a spouse over the personal property of his spouse, without a mandate, is not enforceable against the latter.?",
    "answers": ["Yes", "No, it is null and void"],
    "correctAnswer": "No, it is null and void"
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "As part of a withdrawal of power, Fabrice was authorized to administer the property of his wife Pauline.Can he still receive the fruits?",
    "answers": [
      "Yes, but only after joint agreement of the notary and the judge",
      "Yes, in all cases",
      "Yes, but only with Pauline's agreement"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": " Yes, in all hypotheses "
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "Can a spouse consent to a donation of earnings and wages to his adulterous concubine, if these sums have not been saved?",
    "answers": [
      "Yes, but only if he has fulfilled the duties of the marriage",
      "Yes, always",
      "No, never"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Yes, but only if he has fulfilled the obligations of the marriage"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "Should the third party who received Lucie's property, by his deed of sale, return the property received, even though it is in good faith?",
    "answers": [
      "Yes",
      "Marketing Campaign",
      "No, only the third party in bad faith is obliged to return the property or its value"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "No, only the third party in bad faith is obliged to return the property or its value"
  }
]
